toywiz.com 2018-10-21

# Privacy & Security

Hi! This is our privacy policy and, if you landed here, it means that you want to learn how we process your personal data at ToyWiz.com. We won’t let you down! 

Essential information we collect   
In operating our store, it is essential for us to capture some information about your device, such as your IP address and information related to your visit when you browse our store. For example, this might include time-stamp, the last page or product you visited, the indication that you logged in. We do that in order to: 

  * remember who you are after you log in so that you do not need to authenticate at each click; 
  * monitor if our website is running with the high performance we are dedicated to providing; 
  * let you browse between products without having to start back from the home page at each click;
  * display items or ads you might find interesting;
  * remember if you put something in your shopping cart before you decide to checkout; and
  * control that your data is processed securely.

We call the information mentioned above “essential information” and we collect it through the use of cookies. Cookies are small text files that most websites use. A website places cookies in the web browser and then reads the information collected through the cookies every time the user performs an action. We use cookies. Without enabling this mechanism and this kind of cookies (first-party cookies), we could not provide you with the smooth experience that you expect while you are navigating. 

Order information you expressly provide   
If you buy something from our store, we will need more specific information about you. To fully process your order and ship the merchandise you selected, we need your personal data such as your first and last name, your email address and your shipping and billing address. We also use your contact and order information to send you communication related to the processing of your order. We will ask you to provide this information in our “checkout page” before letting you finalize your purchase with the payment. 

Accounts   
You can sign up for an account if you’d like. This will make us happy because it confirms your interest in our store. It should also make you happy because we will remember your information and, when you decide to buy our products, you do not have to provide all of your information over again -- you just have to log-in. Before registering your account, we will ask you to expressly provide your consent to this privacy policy. Only if you give us your consent, we will open your account. We also you the possibility to easily withdraw your consent and delete your account. Just connect with us at the contact details at the bottom of the page. 

Partial Purchases   
If you have started to buy one of our products, but have not completed the purchase, you may have provided partial information, such as your email. In that case, we might send you an email to remind you about your interest. If you are not comfortable in receiving further emails of this kind, we will give you a simple opportunity to opt-out. Your privacy means a lot to us and we will stop sending you these communications right away. 

Reviews   
If you have completed a purchase, we may send you an email to ask you to review the product you bought. We want to be sure that whether you love your purchase or have a complaint, you can share your opinion with other customers. 

Personalization   
We also use some specific information related to your visit, such as the timestamp of your visit, the page or the product you viewed, where you are coming from (if you came to our store because you clicked on an advertisement or you just opened our direct link). This is very similar to the “essential information,” but we use it to provide you with a personalized experience. The information on your visit provides us with insights on your interests and allows us to send you relevant communications. We capture this information through cookies, called a "beacon." 

Newsletters & Emails  
If you sign up for our newsletters and product updates, we will use the information you provide to us to send regular newsletters. If you have updated your subscription profile with product preferences or if you've purchased from our shop, you may also receive email alerts targeted to your preferences and/or your purchase history. 

How do we process your information?   
We use an external provider to run our store, BigCommerce . BigCommerce is based in the US and is a participant in the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and committed to providing best-in-class service and data protection. You can check its participation in the Privacy Shield on the official site of The International Trade Administration (ITA), U.S. Department of Commerce. 11305 Four Points Drive / Building II, Third Floor / Austin, TX 78726, or contact them at privacy@bigcommerce.com   
Through BigCommerce, we also use other, highly specialized external providers to provide the most competitive services. For example: 

  * Payment: Our store is PCI-DSS compliant (a very strict industry standard with requirements for the security of credit card information), and we use an accredited company to process your credit card information. 
  * Shipping: We integrate with a number of shipping companies to fulfill your orders, primarily with USPS and UPS.
  * Email: We integrate with approved services to process newsletters and email updates

Partnering with highly specialized external companies allows us to focus on what we do best: selling great products. 

How can you control your personal data? If you are one of our customers who is in the EU, and we are specifically selling our products to the Member State where you are located, you have specific rights that we are honored to enforce without undue delay: Access, Correct, Erasure, Port, Object. If you cannot exercise your choice on your account page or if you do not have an account with us, please reach out to us, at the contact details at the bottom of this page. We will be more than happy to help. 

How long do we keep your data? We keep your data for as long as you have an account with us. We also keep some data for security investigation. Most importantly, we have specific obligations for fraud detection and tax reasons. Therefore, we might need to retain certain data even if you ask to delete it. 

Who can you reach out to for privacy matters? You can contact our Data Protection Officer here: privacy@toywiz.com 363 Spook Rock Rd building k Suffern, NY 10901 

Any update? If we update our Privacy Policy to reflect a change or improvement of our services or a new legal obligation, we will publish the new version on our website, and we will make it clear on our home page https://www.toywiz.com so it will be visible as you enter our store. 

Protecting Your Information

**** Safe & secure shopping is our #1 priority. We use a variety of security measures, including sophisticated encryption and authentication tools to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind heavily secured networks. All credit card and personal information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases. 

Collecting Information

**** Unless otherwise noted or you provide us with specific information about yourself, we do not gather personal information. You can visit any of our web pages without telling us who you are. We will only request information from you when you decide to place an order, if you decide to participate in a sweepstakes or opt in for our newsletter.. 

Sharing Information

**** Toywiz.com takes the sharing of your information seriously. **You are under no obligation to register with the site in order to access or use this service.** If you do register with this website, you agree to: (a) provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by the registration form (collectively, "Registration Data"); and (b) maintain and promptly update the Registration Data to keep it accurate, current and complete. In addition to and without limiting in any way the Company's general right to terminate your access and use of the Services, or the Services themselves, as set forth herein, if you provide any information determined by the Company, in its sole discretion, to be untrue, inaccurate, not current, incomplete, misleading or designed to deceive, or if the Company, in its sole discretion, believes it has a basis to suspect that such is the case, the Company has the right to immediately suspend or terminate your account, either with or without notice to you, and refuse to grant any and all current or future access and use of the Services (or any portion thereof) and/or any benefit to which you may be entitled through your access and use of the Services. You also agree that you are solely and completely responsible and liable for any and all activities which occur under your account. In addition, when you register for the Services, you agree to receive an email newsletter that may contain the Company and/or Sponsor offers. You may opt-out of receiving this email newsletter at any time by following the opt-out instructions provided in the email newsletter. Newsletter Opt-In and Third Party Offers. You are not obligated to opt-in to receive the Company's Newsletter. If you do opt-in to receive the Company's Newsletter you also agree to receive select ToyWiz Sponsor offers, that will be designated as such. However, if you choose to opt-out to receive the Newsletter you will stop receiving the Company's news letter promptly, Howerver, you understand and agree that select Toy Wiz Sponsor's may contact you using the registration information you provide to the Company, including without limitation, by telephone or email, pursuant to the terms and conditions of the Company's Privacy Policy. The Company reserves the right to update or modify the number and/or mix of Sponsors' offers, at any time for any reason, in its sole discretion. To opt-out of receiving select Toy Wiz Sponsors' offers please follow the opt-out instructions associated with the Sponsors' offer. Official Sweepstakes Rules. You understand, acknowledge and agree to be bound by the relevant Official Sweepstakes Rules for the sweepstakes you elect to participate in. Compliance with Order Investigations. On rare occasions, when credit card fraud is involved we may share information with companies assisting in the investigation. This is done for the sole purpose of protecting our rights and the security of others. 

Questions and Feedback

**** We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all [feedback](mailto:toywizcustomerservice@yahoo.com?subject=Re:%20ToyWiz%20Privacy%20Policy) pertaining to privacy, or any other issue. 

Copyright Information

All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons & images is the property of ToyWiz or its content suppliers and protected by United States and international copyright laws. The compilation of all content on this site is the exclusive property of ToyWiz and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. 

Terms of Use

By accepting these Terms of Use through your use of the Site, you certify that you are 18 years of age or older. If you are under the age of 18 but at least 13 years of age you may use this Site only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by these Terms of Use. ToyWiz.com does not intentionally collect personal information about children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 may not use this Site other than for browsing, and parents or legal guardians may not agree to these Terms of Use on their behalf. If you are a parent or legal guardian agreeing to these Terms of Use for the benefit of a child between the ages of 13 and 18, be advised that you are fully responsible for his or her use of this Site, including all financial charges and legal liability that he or she may incur. If you do not agree to (or cannot comply with) any of these terms and conditions, do not use this Site. All billing and registration information provided must be truthful and accurate. Providing any untruthful or inaccurate information may constitute a breach of these Terms of Use. By confirming your purchase at the end of the checkout process, you agree to accept and pay for the item(s) requested. Any dispute arising from the use of this site, or transaction with this site, is binding to the state of New York. 

Quantity Limits & Dealer Sales

ToyWiz.com reserves the right, at our sole discretion, to limit the quantity of items purchased per person, per household or per order. These restrictions may be applicable to orders placed by the same credit card and also to orders that use the same billing and/or shipping address. We will provide notification to the customer should such limits be applied to an existing order. 

Pricing Information

While ToyWiz.com strives to provide accurate product and pricing information, pricing or typographical errors may occur. ToyWiz.com cannot confirm the price of an item until after you order. In the event that an item is listed at an incorrect price or with incorrect information due to an error in pricing or product information, ToyWiz.com shall have the right, at our sole discretion, to refuse or cancel any orders placed for the item. In the event that an item is mispriced, ToyWiz.com may, at our discretion, either contact you for instructions or cancel your order and notify you of such cancellation. 

Mint Product Policy & Guarantee

ToyWiz.com prides itself on quality. All figures & toys we sell are guaranteed authentic and "Mint in Sealed Box". This means that the package or box may have minor wear but the toy inside is always guaranteed in mint condition, never touched or played with. 

Privacy Policy

PLEASE NOTE: THE SERVICES ON THIS WEBSITE ARE ONLY AVAILABLE TO INDIVIDUALS 13 YEARS OF AGE OR OLDER (INDIVIDUALS UNDER THE AGE OF 18, THOUGH, MUST OBTAIN THE PERMISSION OF A PARENT OR LEGAL GUARDIAN). IF YOU DO NOT QUALIFY UNDER THESE REQUIREMENTS, YOU ARE NOT AUTHORIZED TO USE OR SUBMIT ANY INFORMATION ON THE WEBSITE OR USE THE SERVICE. Welcome to Toywiz.com website and the services available through this website (collectively, the "Website" or "Service(s)"). Throughout this policy, the Company shall be referred to as "Company," "we" or "us". The website user will be referred to as "You", "User(s)", "Consumer(s)" or "Subscriber(s)". This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") covers the treatment of personally identifiable information that the Company collects when you are on the Website and/or when you sign up for and/or use the Service. It is important that our users are fully informed about the use of their personal information. The Company believes in 100% permission-based marketing. This Privacy Policy also applies to consumers that have agreed to receive e-mail marketing from the Company and the Company's joint marketing advertisers ("Advertisers"), whether at the Website, via e-mail and/or on third-party websites (via co-registration or otherwise). **

Collection of Information by the Company

** **Children's Privacy** This Website is not directed to children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information on this Website from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a visitor under the age of 13, we will delete the information from our records. **

Personally Identifiable Information

** For each user, our web server automatically recognizes the user's domain name and IP address, but not the e-mail address (unless supplied independently by a user). To qualify to receive access to the Website and/or Services, subject to the requirements set forth in our EULA and Website Terms and Conditions, we gather personal information from you in order to establish your Company membership account. This information may include, but is not necessarily limited to, your first and last name, e-mail address, postal mailing address, mobile telephone number and other demographic information, as well as credit/debit card information for payment and/or age verification purposes (collectively, "Personally Identifiable Information" or "PII". IT IS IMPORTANT THAT YOU SUPPLY US WITH VALID, COMPLETE, CURRENT AND ACCURATE PERSONAL IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION; SUCH PII WILL BE USED TO SUPPLY THE SERVICES TO YOU AND TO COLLECT PAYMENT FOR SUCH SERVICES (WHERE APPLICABLE). By submitting your PII, you authorize us to confirm the accuracy of the information you submitted against government-issued identification. We may also collect information related to your online activities to more accurately target and measure our advertising inventory, including, without limitation, the places you visit at the Website, content accessed and associated marketing metrics (such as e-mails opened and responded to) (collectively, your "Marketing Profile"). In addition, if you choose to participate in any offer(s) available at or through the Website, whether offered by us and/or a third party, any Personally Identifiable Information submitted by you shall be subject to the privacy policy(s) of the respective third party(s) collecting such PII. In addition, you may find links to other websites from our Website. Please be aware that the Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties and/or websites. We strongly encourage you to be aware of when you leave our Website and/or supply your Personally Identifiable Information to any third party, and to read the privacy policies of each and every third party and/or website before using such third party website(s) and/or before supplying any PII to them. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this Website. Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information Obtained by Company You understand and agree that the Company may use and share your PII with third parties as needed to supply the Service(s) to you. For example, if you want to use a ringtone that you created on your mobile device, we will transfer your mobile telephone number and the location of the ringtone to a service provider, who will then transmit the ringtone to your mobile device for your personal use. You understand and agree our advertising relationships allow us to make the Company, its Website and/or the Service(s) available to you. Accordingly, the Personally Identifiable Information that you submit to the Company remains your property, but by participating in the Company Website and/or Service(s), you grant us the right to use such PII and your Marketing Profile for multiple marketing purposes, including, but not limited to, sharing such PII with third parties. The Company may use such Personally Identifiable Information to (i) directly market certain offers to you via e-mail marketing, telemarketing, direct mail, mobile telephone text messaging (including, without limitation, SMS and/or MMS) and other methods, (ii) to monitor compliance with our Website EULA and Terms and Conditions, and (iii) for content improvement and feedback purposes. We may sell your Personally Identifiable Information that you supply to us and we may join together with other third-party businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to you. These businesses may include, but are not limited to, providers of online, e-mail, telemarketing and direct mail marketing services and applications. Such services and applications may include, but not be limited to, lookup and reference, data enhancement, overlay, appending, suppression and validation. By registering for toywiz.com, you are indicating that you have read and agree to this Privacy Policy and of its all terms and conditions, and you further acknowledge and agree that you understand how and under what circumstances your Personally Identifiable Information will be used. You also agree to receive marketing promotions and other solicitations from this Website, its advertising partners and/or other third-party advertisers (collectively, "Website Sponsors") based on the PII you provide on this Website, and expressly agree to be contacted by any such Website Sponsors through direct mail, phone, pre-recorded message, SMS text and/or email. In addition to marketing purposes, the Company reserves the right to release your Personally Identifiable Information if: (a) we believe that the Website and/or Service(s) is being or has been used in violation of the EULA and/or Terms and Conditions and/or to commit unlawful acts; (b) your Personally Identifiable Information is subpoenaed or requested by a court, governmental agency or law enforcement entity; or (c) the Company is sold, transferred and/or acquired. Moreover, you hereby consent to the disclosure of any information, record or communication from you to any third party when the Company determines, in its sole discretion, that the disclosure is appropriate or necessary, for example, to share your e-mail address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time. In addition, you agree that by registering for a Company membership, such act constitutes a purchase, inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 CFR 310 et seq. ("Rule"). Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, the Company retains the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the Rule. Moreover, by registering with, or requesting information from, a third-party advertiser at or through the Website, such action shall constitute an inquiry and/or application with the respective third-party advertiser for purposes of the Rule. As such, you may be contacted via e-mail, direct mail and/or telemarketing by such third-party advertiser in accordance with the Rule. To the extent that your credit card-specific information and/or social security number is collected by the Company, said information will be transmitted securely, kept in confidence and will not be shared with any third parties (other than third party service providers - such as payment processors - who provide services to the Company and/or consumer credit agencies) without your prior informed consent. In addition, by submitting your credit card information to us, you authorize the Company to periodically verify by various methods that your credit card account continues to be valid and active, including, without limitation, charging and thereafter immediately crediting a small sum to the credit card. Apart from the foregoing uses, the Company and its affiliates and/or subsidiaries reserve the right to share with third parties the fact that we/they have credit card information on file for you, but such specific credit card information shall not be shared by us/them with any third parties without your prior authorization. You may receive an e-mail confirming your membership with the Company, co-registration with Advertisers, as well as promotional marketing of commercial products and services. The Company reserves the right to collect and retain data relating to e-mail marketing sent to, and opened by, individuals on our marketing list(s). **

Opt-Out Policy

** You may exercise your option to not receive any future communications from us by clicking here. Subscribers should note that unsubscribing from this Website's electronic mailings will not automatically unsubscribe you from any communications you have elected to receive from our Clients or other third parties. Please note that you may still receive information from third parties to whom we have disclosed your Personally Identifiable Information prior to the time you opted-out. The Company Website users who no longer wish to receive promotional e-mail materials from our Advertisers may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions contained in the applicable e-mail, in accordance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003. You must unsubscribe separately from each Advertiser's list. To unsubscribe from any Advertiser's website or e-mail list, please visit their website or review their e-mail for complete "unsubscribe" details. Similarly, if, after unsubscribing from Company emails, you click on or access an Advertiser's offer appearing at the Website, you may begin receiving offers by, or on behalf of, those particular Advertisers. You must unsubscribe from their list in order to stop receiving their email offers. **

Privacy Complaints

** If you believe that we have not complied with this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: privacy@toywiz.com. Please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that this Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate and respond to your complaint as promptly as possible under the circumstances. If you feel that your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you may contact the Direct Marketing Association at privacypromise@the-dma.org or in writing at: Direct Marketing Association: Attn: Privacy Promise, 615 L St. NW, Suite 1100, Washington, DC 20036 **

How to Access or Modify Your Information

** We strive to keep all Personally Identifiable Information current, accurate and complete. You are always fully in control of the PII that we maintain to service you. You can change your PII at any time and as often as necessary. You can also request that any Personally Identifiable Information be deleted. Certain Personally Identifiable Information may be withheld or exempted from deletion if this is required by law or is part of a fraud investigation, or as otherwise described above in the "Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information Obtained By Company" section. You may access and modify your Personally Identifiable Information by contacting us at: privacy@toywiz.com **

Special Notification for California Residents

** Individuals who reside in California and have provided their Personally Identifiable Information may request information regarding disclosures of this information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted to us at the following emailing address: CAPrivacy@toywiz.com This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified above. **

General information collection and use - Aggregate

** We gather our users' server, IP address and browser-type related information in the general administration of our Website and Service(s). The Company reserves the right to transfer and/or sell aggregate or group data about the Company users for lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage or other characteristics of the Company's users as a group, without disclosing Personally Identifiable Information. By submitting your Personally Identifiable Information to, and/or using, the Website and/or Service(s), you agree to allow the Company to transfer and/or sell such aggregate data to third parties. **Log Files** Like most website servers, we use log files. Log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Log file information is not linked to Personally Identifiable Information. **

Use of Cookies

** A cookie is a text file stored on a user's hard drive containing information about the respective user. Cookies can provide great convenience for users at many websites and is required to use the Company Website and Service(s). For instance, by associating a cookie with your computer which is identified and processed by our servers, you need not log in more than once at the Website, thereby saving time and convenience while using our servers. In particular, we may use persistent and/or session cookies at the Website. Persistent cookies do not automatically expire, but persist to permit the Company to register future visits at the Website with your profile in our servers. In addition, cookies associated with the Company may be read, aggregated and used with cookies associated with other affiliate Internet properties. In addition, we and/or third parties that advertise at the Website and through other types of media available at or through the Website may use cookies and pixel gifs to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Website and/or for advertising tracking purposes. **

Third Party Cookies

** The Company delivers to your web browser many of the advertisements you see when you use the Website. However, the Company also allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within and/or on the Website. Because your web browser must request these advertising banners from the ad networks' servers, these companies can send their own cookies to your cookie file, just as if you had requested a web page from the Website. Please note that if an Advertiser asks the Company to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 13-24 who have viewed sports content) and you respond to that ad, the Advertiser and/or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. However, the Company only authorizes our third-party ad servers to employ anonymous cookies for ad delivery and anonymous targeting. To the Company's knowledge, the third-party ad servers do not collect Personally Identifiable Information about you. In addition, the Company uses third-party service provider partners to employ anonymous cookies for accounting and data integrity purposes. If you want to prevent a third-party ad server and/or third-party service provider from sending and reading cookies on your computer, currently you must visit each ad network's and service provider's website individually and opt-out (if they offer this capability). Currently, we have relationships with third party service providers and/or may display third party ad server networks ([click to visit their website](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#%21/)). In addition, we may at some point engage other third-party ad servers and/or third-party service providers in the future. You can set your browser to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. For further information on cookies please visit http://www.aboutcookies.org. **

Security

** To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Although we take reasonable technological precautions to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. When a user submits sensitive personal and payment information via the Website, the information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration, download or purchase process prompts a user to enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number), the information is encrypted and is protected with industry-standard encryption - SSL technology. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also use commercially reasonable measures to protect user information off-line. Access to user information is restricted in our offices and areas where such information is stored. Only employees and authorized individuals who need access to the information to perform a specific job are granted access to Personally Identifiable Information. If you have any questions about the security at our Website, please contact us at security@toywiz.com. **

Changes to This Privacy Policy

** We reserve the right, at our sole discretion and at any time, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Website. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Company Website and/or Service(s) following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of such changes. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you may not use and/or access the Website and/or Service(s). **Your Acceptance of this Privacy Policy** By using this Website and/or Service(s), you agree to all of the terms and conditions of the Company Privacy Policy, as well as all other policies contained on the Website and relating to the Services. **Questions? Contact us** If you have any questions about our privacy practices or your dealings with the service, please do not hesitate to contact us at: ToyWiz.com 363 Spook Rock, Building K Suffern, NY 109011.
